<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kim Sellis Yoga</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/</link><description>Recent content on Kim Sellis Yoga</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 12:39:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kimsellis.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 13:55:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/about/</guid><description>Kim is a former pharmaceutical biologist originally from Chicago. Her love for fitness began at an early age as a competitive gymnast. Since then, she has trained as a triathlete and achieved her 1st Dan in Shotokan Karate. Making the jump from her pharmaceutical career, she became an accredited personal trainer and yoga instructor.
Kim’s yoga stems from her love of science and sport. She is welcoming, motivational and teaches to everyone’s unique anatomy.</description></item><item><title>New Students</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/students/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/students/</guid><description>What is Vinyasa Yoga? Vinyasa is a style of yoga in which students flow from one pose to next. Once familiar with the poses and basic shapes yogis start to create a practice with smooth transitions and syncing breath to the movement. Vinyasa yoga is an active yoga so you should be able to easily move from the ground to standing positions.
My classes are flowing movements combined with longer holds to catch our breath.</description></item><item><title>Classes</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/classes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 11:33:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/classes/</guid><description>Yoga at The Proud Project Location: 227-229 Chiswick High Rd., Chiswick W4 2DX. Classes Start January 3, 2023
Tuesday 12:30pm Beginner Vinyasa
Thursday 12:30pm Beginner Vinyasa
Thursday 1:30pm Vinyasa Flow
Yoga at Snap Fitness Chiswick Group yoga classes are back in the fitness studio. Non-club members can join these classes by buying a day pass (£10). Call reception to book. Phone: 020 8987 0262
Location: 500 Chiswick High Rd, Chiswick, London W4 5RG</description></item><item><title>Breathing</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/breathing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 15:54:26 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/breathing/</guid><description>Yoga Breathing and Breath Coaching There are many benefits associated with breath practices.
Improve Sleep Enhance Digestion Boost Immune Response Build Focus and Mental Clarity Reduce Anxiety and Stress Skeptical? Me too!
So I dug deeper. There is a growing body of scientific research to back up all of these claims. I have experienced the benefits for myself and have seen the results in my clients. Breath can positively impact your physical and emotional health.</description></item><item><title>COVID-Secure</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/covid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 11:33:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/covid/</guid><description>Even though extra precautions due to Covid-19 are being taken, I am participating at my own risk. I understand that even if all the guidelines are followed, there is a risk of contracting the virus.
General Guidelines to be followed All government guidelines relating to Covid-19 should be followed. Students should not to attend classes if they are or think they might be in breach of these these guidelines (re: return travel, flu like systems etc.</description></item><item><title>Corporate Classes</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/ctas/corporate_contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 12:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/ctas/corporate_contact/</guid><description>Interested in corporate classes for your workplace?
Contact Kim Now</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 13:55:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/privacy/</guid><description>At Kim Sellis Yoga, accessible from https://kimsellis.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Kim Sellis Yoga and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Kim Sellis Yoga.</description></item><item><title>Terms</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/terms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/terms/</guid><description>Welcome to Kim Sellis Yoga!
These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of Kim Sellis Yoga&amp;rsquo;s Website, located at https://kimsellis.com.
By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use Kim Sellis Yoga if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.
The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: &amp;ldquo;Client&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Your&amp;rdquo; refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company’s terms and conditions.</description></item><item><title>Waiver</title><link>https://kimsellis.com/waiver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kimsellis.com/waiver/</guid><description>Assumption of Risk I state that I wish to participate in yoga activities that may include aerobic exercise, resistance exercise and stretching. I agree to do so at my own risk, I am voluntarily participating, assume all risk of injury to myself, and agree to release and discharge Kim Sellis Yoga from any and all claims or causes of action, known or unknown, arising out of Kim Sellis Yoga.
I will stop exercising immediately if I feel dizzy, faint, light-headed or if I experience any discomfort.</description></item></channel></rss>